OLADOKUN JOSEPH OLAMIDE

Epe Lagos | Olamideanuoluwapo40@gmail.com | 08184523486 |

PROFILE

Reliable Employee & Team Player with energetic and resourceful customer service and good professional work ethics and promoting conflict resolution. Ability to cultivate key client relationships for multiple campaigns in diverse industries. Expertise in client services, account management and relationship-building.

WORK HISTORY

Divine Success Cyber Cafe

June 2014 - December 2014

Position: Café Attendants

- Promptly respond to customer enquiries in person or via phone, email, or social media.
- Quickly and efficiently open customer accounts by accurately recording account information.
- Maintain financial accounts by processing customer adjustments in a professional manner.
- Increased company's growth by 50% due to the delivery of quick service.

Adc Tutorial January 2017 – December 2018

Position: Tutor

EDUCATION

CCCE

SSCE	2017	
O' Level result		
Blessed Ave Maria Schools+, Lagos.	(2017)	
CERTIFICATION/TRAINING		
Jobberman Soft Skills Training Certification	2021	
English and Writing Mastery Course Certification	2020	
Fundamentals of the English Grammar Certification	2021	
Microsoft Office Certification	2018	
Copywriting Course (A free course on YouTube, no certification)	2022	
Introduction to Front-End Development (Coursera)	2023	

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

TEDx LASU- Non-Profit Organization

December 2021- PRESENT

2017

- Volunteer as a deputy team lead of the Publicity and Content Creation of the community.
- Supervised a team of sixteen people to ensure the successful completion of the Saloon event and Annual event.

Nigerian Institution of Mechanical Engineers - Engineering society

October 2021 - PRESENT

- Worked as a volunteer to support the Mechanical Engineering week and Annual Symposium.
- Developed oneness and building a good team spirit amongst every member of the team.
- Worked as the assistant secretary of the society and helped to maintain proper documentation in keeping records of all relevant reports of the society.
- Kept record of all relevant reports and documents.

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS

- Student Member, Nigerian Institution of Mechanical Engineers (February 2021 present)
- Society of Petroleum Engineers
- TEDx Lagos State University (October 2021 present)

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

- Personal Effectiveness
- Excellent organisational skills
- Highly Proficient in Computer applications; (Photoshop, MS Office, HTML, CSS)
- Highly Proficient in Programming Languages; (JAVASCRIPT)
- Good Problem Solving Skills
- Good communication skills
- Writing Skills: Written articles on finance and health issues, Report for meetings
- Strength: Information Documentation, Programme Implementation, Creative Thinking
- Interest: Education, Music, Youth Transition and Research

REFEREES

Available on request